<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<cockatrice_carddatabase version='4'>
	<sets>
		<set>
			<name>PKM</name>
			<longname>Pokemon World</longname>
			<settype>Custom</settype>
			<releasedate>2026-04-15</releasedate>
		</set>
	</sets>
	<cards>
		<card>
			<name>Bulbasaur</name>
			<text>Leech Seed — Whenever Bulbasaur enters or becomes evolved, put a seed counter on up to one target creature an opponent controls.
Whenever a creature with one or more seed counter dies, its controller loses 1 life and you gain 1 life.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/0.png" num="169">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant Beast</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>BG</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ivysaur</name>
			<text>Evolution Bulbasaur {B}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Bulbasaur you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Reach
Whenever Ivysaur becomes evolved or attacks, you may put a Seed counter on up to two target creatures.
Poison Powder — At the beginning of your end step, each opponent loses 1 life for each creature they control with a seed counter on it.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/1.png" num="187">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant Beast</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2BG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Venusaur</name>
			<text>Evolution Ivysaur {2}{B}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Ivysaur you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Trample 
If one or more seed counters would be placed on a creature an opponent controls, that many plus one seed counters are placed on it instead.
Solar Beam — {3}{G}, {T}: Venusaur deals damage equal to its power to target creature you don&apos;t control. Then if it is sunny, untap Venusaur.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/2.png" num="210">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant Beast</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BGG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Venusaur</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Venusaur {3}{B}{G} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Venusaur you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever Mega Venusaur becomes evolved, put a seed counter on each creature your opponents control and a +1/+1 counter on each creature you control.
Thick Fat — If a red source or a snow source would deal damage to Mega Venusaur, prevent half that damage, rounded down.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/3.png" num="193">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Plant Beast</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4BBGG</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/8</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Venusaur</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Venusaur {4}{B}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Venusaur you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Trample
G-Max Vine Lash — When Gigantamax Venusaur becomes evolved, destroy target permanent and return up to one target creature card and up to one target land card from your graveyard to the battlefield.
Whenever a creature an opponent controls dies, you may put a seed counter on up to one target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/4.png" num="179">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Plant Beast</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>6BBGG</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>10/10</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Charmander</name>
			<text>Gather Fire — At the beginning of your precombat main phase, add {R} plus an additional {R} for each card under Charmander. 
Whenever Charmander attacks, it deals damage equal to half its power rounded down to target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/5.png" num="106">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Lizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>RR</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Charmeleon</name>
			<text>Evolution Charmander {R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Charmander you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Menace
Whenever Charmeleon enters or becomes evolved, add {R}{R}. 
Solar Power — As long as it is sunny, red spells you cast cost {1} less to cast and red creatures you control have +1/+.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/6.png" num="107">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Lizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2RR</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Charizard</name>
			<text>Evolution Charmeleon {2}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Charmeleon you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying
If a red creature you control would deal damage to an opponent or a permanent an opponent controls, it deals that much damage plus 1 instead.
Flamethrower — Whenever you spend mana produced by a pokémon to cast a red spell, Charizard deals 3 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/7.png" num="105">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Lizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Charizard X</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Charizard {3}{R}{R} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Charizard you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying, double strike
Inferno X — When Mega Charizard X becomes evolved, pokémon you control gain double strike and trample until the end of the turn. 
Damage that would be dealt by Mega Charizard X can&apos;t be prevented.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/8.png" num="127">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Lizard Dragon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>8/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Charizard Y</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Charizard {3}{R}{R} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Charizard you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying
Whenever a pokémon you control produces one or more mana, it produces that much plus an additional {R}.
At the beginning of your precombat main phase, if it&apos;s sunny, add {R} for each red creature you control.
Drought — When Mega Charizard Y becomes evolved, it becomes sunny.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/9.png" num="128">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Lizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/8</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Charizard</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Charizard {4}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Charizard you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Flying, trample
Whenever a creature an opponent controls is dealt excess damage, Gigantamax Charizard deals that much damage to that creature&apos;s controller. cost 
G-Max Wildfire — Whenever Gigantamax Charizard becomes evolved or attacks, it deals 3 damage to each opponent and each creature they control. cost</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/10.png" num="113">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Lizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>6RRRR</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>10/10</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Squirtle</name>
			<text>Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Withdraw — Whenever Squirtle enters or becomes evolved, you may return another target creature you control to its owner&apos;s hand. If you do, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/11.png" num="77">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Turtle</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>UU</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Wartortle</name>
			<text>Evolution Squirtle {U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Squirtle you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flash
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Whenever Wartortle enters or becomes evolved, target creature you control gains hexproof until end of turn.
Rain Dance — Whenever you return one or more creatures you control to your hand, it starts to rain.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/12.png" num="81">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Turtle</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>
Blastoise</name>
			<text>Evolution Wartortle {2}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Wartortle you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf, ward {3} (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Hydro Pump — Whenever Blastoise becomes evolved or attacks, you may return target creature with mana value less than or equal to Blastoise&apos;s mana value to its owner&apos;s hand.
Whenever another blue creature enters the battlefield under your control, if Blastoise is tapped, untap it and draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/13.png" num="33">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Turtle</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UUU</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Blastoise</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Blastoise {3}{U}{U} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Blastoise you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Mega Launcher — Whenever you activate or trigger an ability of a blue creature you control, copy that ability. You may choose new targets for the copy.
When Mega Blastoise becomes evolved, you may return up to one target nonland permanent to its owner&apos;s hand.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/14.png" num="62">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Turtle</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5UUU</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/9</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Blastoise</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Blastoise {4}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Blastoise you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Surf, Trample (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
G-Max Cannonade — Whenever Gigantamax Blastoise becomes evolved, return all non-Gigantamax nonland permanents your opponents control to their owners hands.
Whenever a creature is returned to its owners hand, untap target land you control.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/15.png" num="47">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Turtle</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>6UUUU</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>10/10</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Caterpie</name>
			<text>Shield Dust — Whenever one or more creatures attack you, target attacking creature gets -1/-0 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/16.png" num="146">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>G</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metapod</name>
			<text>Evolution Caterpie {G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Caterpie you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Harden — {0}:Prevent the next 2 damage that would be dealt to Metapod. Activate this ability only once each turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/17.png" num="153">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2G</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>0/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Butterfree</name>
			<text>Evolution Metapod {G}{G}. (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Metapod you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying
When Butterfree becomes evolved, you may put up to two cards from under it into their owner&apos;s graveyards. Draw a card for each card put into a graveyard this way.
Stun Spore — Whenever Butterfree attacks, you may put a stun counter on up to one target creature defending player controls.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/18.png" num="145">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Butterfree</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Butterfree {5}{G}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Butterfree you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Flying, Ward {3}
G-Max Befuddle — When Gigantamax Butterfree becomes evolved, tap all creatures your opponents control, then put a stun counter on each of those creatures.
Whenever an insect you control deals combat damage to a player, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/19.png" num="150">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7GGG</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Weedle</name>
			<text>Poison Sting — Whenever Weedle deals combat damage to a creature, put a -1/-1 counter on that creature.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/20.png" num="219">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>B/G</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Kakuna</name>
			<text>Evolution Weedle {BG} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Weedle you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Harden — {0}:Prevent the next 2 damage that would be dealt to Kakuna. Activate this ability only once each turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/21.png" num="217">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2B/G</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>0/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Beedrill</name>
			<text>Evolution Kakuna {B}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Kakuna you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
First strike
When Beedrill becomes evolved, you may pay {1}{BG}, If you do put up to 2 cards from under Beedrill onto the battlefield.
Swarm — Whenever Beedrill attacks, other attacking insect pokémon you control gain +1/+1 until the end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/22.png" num="216">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2B/GB/G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Beedrill</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Beedrill {3}{B}{G} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Beedrill you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Double strike
Hazard Stinger — Whenever Mega Beedrill deals combat damage to a player, if it was cast for it&apos;s mega evolution cost, that player loses half their life, rounded up.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/23.png" num="218">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5B/GB/GB/G</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Pidgey</name>
			<text>Flying
Gust — Whenever Pidgey enters or evolves, up to one target creature can&apos;t attack during its controllers next turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/24.png" num="26">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>W</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Pidgeotto</name>
			<text>Evolution Pidgey {W}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Pidgey you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying, Vigilance
Whirlwind — Whenever Pidgeotto attacks, you may tap target creature with toughness 2 or less. It can&apos;t attack during its controllers next turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/25.png" num="25">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3W</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Pidgeot</name>
			<text>Evolution Pidgeotto {2}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Pidgeotto you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying, first strike
Feather Dance — Whenever Pidgeot attacks, other attacking creatures you control with flying get +1/+1 until end of turn. Then if you attacked with three or more creatures this turn, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/26.png" num="24">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4WW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Pidgeot</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Pidgeot {3}{W}{W} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Pidgeot you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying, first strike
Hurricane — When Mega Pidgeot becomes evolved, other creatures you control gain +1/+1 and flying until end of turn. Creatures can&apos;t attack you or planeswalkers you control unless their controller pays {1} for each of those creatures, until the start of your next turn.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/27.png" num="21">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5WWW</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rattata</name>
			<text>When Rattata enters or becomes evolved, put a +1/+1 counter on another target creature you control.
Bite — Whenever Rattata attacks, it gets +X/+0 where X is equal to the number of other creatures you control.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/28.png" num="28">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mouse</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>W</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Rattata</name>
			<text>When Alolan Rattata enters or evolves, surveil 1.
Gluttony — Whenever Alolan Rattata deals combat damage to a player, create a food token.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/29.png" num="215">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mouse</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>W/B</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>WB</colors>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Raticate</name>
			<text>Evolution Rattata {W}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Rattata you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
First strike
When Raticate enters or becomes evolved, create a Rattata token.
Super Fang — Whenever Raticate deals combat damage to a player, that player loses life equal to the number of creatures you control.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/30.png" num="27">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mouse</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Raticate</name>
			<text>Evolution Alolan Rattata {W}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Alolan Rattata you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Menace
Hustle — Whenever Alolan Raticate enters or becomes evolved, create two food tokens.
Whenever Alolan Raticate attacks, you may sacrifice a food. If you do, target opponent loses life equal to the number of creatures you control.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/31.png" num="214">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mouse</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2W/BW/B</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WB</colors>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Spearow</name>
			<text>Flying
Peck — Whenever Spearow attacks, if you control another attacking Bird, Spearow gets +1/+0 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/32.png" num="30">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Fearow</name>
			<text>Evolution Spearow {2}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Spearow you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying, vigilance
Drill Peck — Whenever Fearow attacks, you may pay {1}{W}, if you do Fearow gains first strike until end of turn.
Whenever you attack with three or more birds, create a Spearow creature token.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/33.png" num="11">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WW</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ekans</name>
			<text>Intimidate
Poison Spit — Whenever Ekans enters or evolves, put a -1/-1 counter on up to one target creature.
Wrap — Whenever Ekans blocks a creature, you pay {1}{B} and tap Ekans, if you do, prevent all damage deal to Ekans by that creature and that creature doesn&apos;t untap during its controller&apos;s next untap step.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/34.png" num="87">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Snake</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Arbok</name>
			<text>Evolution Ekans {1}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Ekans you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Intimidate, Menace
Poison Fang — Whenever Arbok attacks, you may put a -1/-1 counter on up to one target creature.
Whenever a creature an opponent controls with a -1/-1 counter on it dies, its controller loses 2 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/35.png" num="86">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Snake</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2BB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Pikachu</name>
			<text>Volt Tackle — Whenever Pikachu attacks, put a charge counter on it, then it deals damage equal to the number of charge counters on it to any target.
Discharge — Remove three charge counters from Pikachu: Add {R}{R}{R}. Exile the top card of your library. Until end of turn, you may play that card.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/36.png" num="135">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mouse Squirrel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Pikachu</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Pikachu {4}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Pikachu you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Trample
G-Max Volt Crash — When Gigantamax Pikachu becomes evolved, it deals X damage to each opponent and each creature they control where X is equal to the number of charge counters on Gigantamax Pikachu.
Whenever a charge counter would be placed on a creature you control, put that many +2 counters on it instead.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/37.png" num="115">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Mouse Squirrel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Raichu</name>
			<text>Evolution Pikachu {2}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Pikachu you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Trample, haste
Energize —Whenever a creature you control with a charge counter deals combat damage to a player, put a charge counter on Raichu.
Thunderbolt — Remove all charge counters from Raichu: It deals damage to any target equal to the number of counters removed this way.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/38.png" num="138">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mouse Squirrel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4RR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Raichu</name>
			<text>Evolution Pikachu {1}{U}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Pikachu you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf, haste (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Surge Surfer —Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, put a charge counter on Alolan Raichu.
Electric Surfer — Whenever Alolan Raichu attacks, you may remove three charge counters from it, if you do it deals 3 damage to any target. Scry 2, then draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/39.png" num="167">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mouse Squirrel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4UR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Raichu X</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Raichu {3}{R}{R} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Raichu you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
When Mega Raichu X becomes evolved, put three charge counters on it. 
Whenever Mega Raichu X attacks, put a charge counter on each creature you control. Creatures you control with charge counters gain +1/+1 and first strike until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/40.png" num="129">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Mouse Squirrel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Raichu Y</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Raichu {3}{R}{R} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Raichu you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
When Mega Raichu Y becomes evolved, put four charge counters on it.
At the beginning of combat on your turn, you may remove any number of charge counters from Mega Raichu Y. When you do, Mega Raichu Y deals that much damage divided as you choose among any number of targets. If three or more charge counters were removed this way, Mega Raichu Y gains double strike until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/41.png" num="130">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Mouse Squirrel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sandshrew</name>
			<text>Dig (At the beginning of your end step, if this creature has attacked this turn, it phases out.)
When Sandshrew enters, a sandstorm rages.
Sand Attack — Whenever Sandshrew attacks or evolves, you may untap target land. If the land is a desert or a sandstorm rages, scry 1.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/42.png" num="157">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mouse Armadillo</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Sandshrew</name>
			<text>When Alolan Sandshrew enters, it begins to snow.
Powder Snow— Whenever Alolan Sandshrew enters or evolves, tap target creature an opponent controls.That creature doesn&apos;t untap during its controller&apos;s next untap step. If it is snowing, scry 1.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/43.png" num="36">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Artifact Creature — Pokémon Mouse Armadillo</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sandslash</name>
			<text>Evolution Sandshrew {1}{G}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Sandshrew you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Dig, vigilance (At the beginning of your end step, if this creature has attacked this turn, it phases out. Attacking doesn&apos;t cause this creature to tap.)
Whenever Sandslash enters or becomes evolved, if a sandstorm rages, search your library for a basic land card or a desert card, put it onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle.
Slash — As long as Sandslash is attacking, it assigns combat damage equal to its toughness rather than its power.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/44.png" num="158">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mouse Armadillo</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3GG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Sandslash</name>
			<text>Evolution Alolan Sandshrew {1}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Alolan Sandshrew you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Ward {2}
Snow Cloak  — At the beginning of combat on your turn, if it is snowing, draw a card.
When Alolan Sandslash enters or becomes evolved, if it is snowing, tap up to two target creatures.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/45.png" num="37">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Artifact Creature — Pokémon Mouse Armadillo</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Nidoran(Female)</name>
			<text>Call the Pack — Whenever Nidoran(Female) enters or evolves, look at the top three cards of your library. You may reveal a pokémon from among them and put the revealed cards into your hand. Put the rest on the bottom of your library in any order.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/46.png" num="98">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Rabbit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Nidorina</name>
			<text>Evolution Nidoran(Female) {B}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target Nidoran(Female) you own. It evolves into this creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Poison Sting — Whenever Nidorina becomes evolved, or attacks, put a –1/–1 counter on up to one target creature.
Whenever a creature an opponent controls with a –1/–1 counter on it dies, you gain 1 life and draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/47.png" num="100">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Rabbit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3B</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Nidoqueen</name>
			<text>Evolution Nidorina {3}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Nidorina you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Vigilance
Queen&apos;s Call — When Nidoqueen enters or becomes evolved, you may return target pokémon rabbit from your graveyard to your hand.
Whenever a pokémon rabbit enters the battlefield under your control, put a -1/-1 counter on up to one target creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/48.png" num="197">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Rabbit Rhino</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BBG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Nidoran(Male)</name>
			<text>Defense of the Pack — Whenever Nidoran(Male) attacks, if you control another pokémon rabbit, you may put a -1/-1 counter on target creature.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/49.png" num="99">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Rabbit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Nidorino</name>
			<text>Evolution Nidoran(Male) {B}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target Nidoran(Male) you own. It evolves into this creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Fury Attack — Whenever Nidorino attacks, if you control another pokémon rabbit, Nidorino gains first strike until end of turn.
At the beginning of each end step, if a pokémon you control died this turn, put a +1/+1 counter on Nidorino.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/50.png" num="101">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Rabbit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3B</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Nidoking</name>
			<text>Evolution Nidorino {3}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Nidorino you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Trample
Whenever Nidoking becomes evolved, or attacks, distribute two –1/–1 counters among up to two target creatures.
King&apos;s Decree — At the beginning of combat on your turn, other pokémon rabbits you control get +1/+1 until end of turn for each card under Nidoking.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/51.png" num="196">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Rabbit Rhino</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BBG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Clefairy</name>
			<text>Whenever a non-token creature enters the battlefield under your control, you gain 1 life.
Metronome — Whenever gain life, you may pay {2}. When you do, choose one —
• Create a Clefairy creature token.
• Tap target creature.
• Return target pokémon card from your graveyard to your hand.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/52.png" num="6">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fairy</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Clefable</name>
			<text>Evolution Clefairy {W}{W}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Clefairy you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Magic Guard — Fairy creatures you control have ward {1}
Whenever Clefable enters or evolves, put a +1/+1 counter on each other creature you control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/53.png" num="5">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fairy</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4WW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Clefable</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Clefable {3}{W}{W} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Clefable you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying
Levitation — If Mega Clefable was cast for it&apos;s mega evolution cost, put a flying counter on each other creature you control.
Whenever Mega Clefable attacks, you gain life equal to the number of creatures you control.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/54.png" num="19">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Fairy</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5WW</manacost>
				<cmc>7</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Vulpix</name>
			<text>Drought — At the beginning of your upkeep, if you control three or more red creatures, it becomes sunny.
Whenever Vulpix enters or evolves, Vulpix deals 1 damage to any target. If it is sunny, Vulpix deals 3 damage instead.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/55.png" num="141">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Vulpix</name>
			<text>Snow Warning — At the beginning of your upkeep, if you control three or more snow creatures, it starts to snow.
Whenever Alolan Vulpix enters or evolves, tap up to one target creature and put a stun counter on it. Then ff it is snowing, scry 1, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/56.png" num="38">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ninetales</name>
			<text>Evolution Vulpix {R}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Vulpix you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
At the beginning of your upkeep, add {R}{R}. Then if there is a card under Nintails, exile the top card of your library, you may play cards exiled this way until the end of your next turn.
Lure — Whenever Ninetales attacks, goad target creature you don&apos;t control. (Until your next turn, that creature attacks each combat if able and attacks a player other than you if able.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/57.png" num="132">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Ninetales</name>
			<text>Evolution Alolan Vulpix {U}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Alolan Vulpix you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Vigilance, Ward {1}
Ice Barrier — Whenever Alolan Ninetales enters or evolves, put a shield counter on each other creature you control.
Whenever Alolan Ninetales attacks, snow creatures you control gain lifelink until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/58.png" num="166">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Creature — Pokémon Fox Fairy</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Jigglypuff</name>
			<text>Lullaby — At the beginning of combat on your turn, you may put a stun counter on target creature. 
Whenever a stun counter is placed on a creature you don&apos;t control, put a +1/+1 counter on Jigglypuff.
Whenever a stun counter is removed from a creature you don&apos;t control, remove a +1/+1 counter from Jigglypuff. When a counter is removed this way, gain 3 life.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/59.png" num="15">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fairy Balloon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Wigglytuff</name>
			<text>Evolution Jigglypuff {W}{W}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Jigglypuff you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Absorb 2 (If a source would deal damage to this creature, prevent 2 of that damage.)
Sleepy Song — Whenever Wigglytuff becomes evolved, tap all creatures you don&apos;t control and put a stun counter on them.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/60.png" num="32">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fairy Balloon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4WW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Zubat</name>
			<text>Flying
Leech Life — Whenever Zubat attacks, defending player loses 1 life and you gain 1 life.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/61.png" num="103">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Golbat</name>
			<text>Evolution Zubat {2}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Zubat you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying
Night Ambush — Whenever an opponent loses life, bats you control gain +1/+1 and menace until end of turn. This ability triggers only once each turn.
When Golbat dies, you may pay {B}{B}, if you do return all creature cards that were under Golbat to the battlefield.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/62.png" num="92">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Oddish</name>
			<text>When Oddish enters, mill three cards. Then return a plant or land card from your graveyard to your hand.
Sprout — Whenever a nontoken plant or land enters under your control, you may put a seed counter on target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/63.png" num="198">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>BG</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gloom</name>
			<text>Evolution Oddish {B}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Oddish you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Foul Nectar — Whenever Gloom becomes evolved or attacks, choose one, if it is sunny, choose both instead -
• Put a +1/+1 counter on another target plant you control.
• Put a seed counter on target creature you don&apos;t control. That creature can&apos;t block this turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/64.png" num="180">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2BG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Vileplume</name>
			<text>Evolution Gloom {2}{B}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Gloom you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Pollen Scatter — Whenever Vileplume becomes evolved, put a seed counter on each creature target opponent controls.
At the beginning of your end step, you may remove X seed counters from among permanents your opponents control. Put target plant with mana value X or less from your graveyard onto the battlefield under your control with a +1/+1 counter on it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/65.png" num="212">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BGG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Paras</name>
			<text>At the beginning of your upkeep, put a spore counter on Paras. You gain 1 life.
Spore — {1}{G}, Remove three spore counters from Paras : Prevent all combat damage dealt by target creature this turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/66.png" num="154">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fungus Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Parasect</name>
			<text>Evolution Paras {1}{G}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Paras you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Effect Spore — At the beginning of your upkeep, put a spore counter on each green creature you control. You gain life equal to the number of counters placed this way.
Remove X spore counters from among creatures you control: Return target creature from your graveyard with mana value X to your hand. Creatures you removed counters from this way get +1/+1 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/67.png" num="155">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fungus Insect Zombie</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3GG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Venonat</name>
			<text>Signal Beam — At the beginning of combat on your turn, up to one target creature must block Venonat this combat if able.
Whenever Venonat is blocked, tap all creatures blocking Venonat and put a stun counter them.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/68.png" num="209">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1BG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Venomoth</name>
			<text>Evolution Venonat {B}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Venonat you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying
Venom Powder — Whenever Venomoth becomes evolved or attacks, you may put a -1/-1 counter on each of up to two target creatures.
Whenever a creature an opponent controls with a -1/-1 counter on it dies, that player loses 1 life and you draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/69.png" num="208">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Diglett</name>
			<text>Dig (At the beginning of your end step, if this creature has attacked this turn, it phases out.)
When a desert enters under your control, a sandstorm rages.
Whenever a sandstorm rages, draw a card.
Dig Under — Whenever Diglett attacks, you may put a land from your hand onto the battlefield tapped. If you don&apos;t, put a +1/+1 counter on Diglett.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/70.png" num="148">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mole</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Diglett</name>
			<text>Dig (At the beginning of your end step, if this creature has attacked this turn, it phases out.)
When Alolan Diglett enters, a sandstorm rages.
Iron Head — At the beginning of your end step, if Alolan Diglett attacked this turn, mill three cards. You may put a land card from among them into your hand. If you don&apos;t, put a +1/+1 counter on Alolan Diglett.
Alolan Diglett has ward {1} as long as a sandstorm rages.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/71.png" num="143">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Pokémon Mole</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dugtrio</name>
			<text>Evolution Diglett {1}{G}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Diglett you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Dig (At the beginning of your end step, if this creature has attacked this turn, it phases out.)
As long as a sandstorm rages, prevent all damage dealt to Dugtrio when it fights a creature.
Magnitude — Whenever Dugtrio enters or becomes evolved, you may have it deal damage to target creature equal to the number of lands you control.
Whenever a land enters the battlefield under your control, you may have Dugtrio fight up to one target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/72.png" num="149">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Mole</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2GGG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Dugtrio</name>
			<text>Evolution Alolan Diglett {1}{G}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Alolan Diglett you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Vigilance, Dig (At the beginning of your end step, if this creature has attacked this turn, it phases out.)
As long as a sandstorm rages, you may play lands from your graveyard.
Gold Rush — {G}{G}{G}: Return target land from your graveyard to the battlefield tapped. Create a treasure token.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/73.png" num="144">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Pokémon Mole</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2GGG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Meowth</name>
			<text>Pay Day — Whenever Meowth deals combat damage to a player, create a treasure token.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/74.png" num="22">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Cat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Meowth</name>
			<text>At the beginning of your end step, if you control three or more Treasures, each opponent loses 1 life and you gain 1 life.
All for One — Whenever an opponent sacrifices a nonland permanent, create a treasure token.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/75.png" num="83">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Cat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Meowth</name>
			<text>Hone Claws — Whenever Galarian Meowth attacks, you may sacrifice a noncreature artifact. If you do, Galarian Meowth gets +1/+1 and gains menace until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/76.png" num="221">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Pokémon Cat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Meowth</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Meowth {4}{W}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Meowth you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Vigilance
G-Max Gold Rush — When Gigantamax Meowth becomes evolved, create five Treasure tokens.
Treasures you control have &quot;{T}, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any one color. Put a +1/+1 counter on up to one target creature. Gain 3 life.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/77.png" num="13">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Cat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7WWW</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Persian</name>
			<text>Evolution Meowth {1}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Meowth you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
When Persian enters or becomes evolved, create two treasure tokens.
Pounce — {1}, Sacrifice a Treasure: Persian gets +2/+0 and gains first strike until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/78.png" num="23">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Cat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WW</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Persian</name>
			<text>Evolution Alolan Meowth {1}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Alolan Meowth you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Menace
Whenever Alolan Persian becomes evolved or deals combat damage to a player, that player discards a card. If the player can&apos;t, create two treasure tokens.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/79.png" num="85">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Cat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BBB</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Psyduck</name>
			<text>When Psyduck enters, it starts to rain.
Headache — {U}{U}, {T}: Counter target noncreature spell. Put a stun counter on Psyduck.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/80.png" num="70">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1UU</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Golduck</name>
			<text>Evolution Psyduck {3}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Psyduck you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Psyshock— Whenever a stun counter is placed on Golduck, you may move it to another target creature.
Whenever Golduck deals combat damage to a player, if it is raining, untap Golduck and draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/81.png" num="51">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mankey</name>
			<text>Anger — Whenever you are attacked by one or more creatures, if Mankey is tapped, you may have Mankey fight target attacking creature. (Each deals damage equal to its power to the other.)</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/82.png" num="126">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Boar Ape</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Primeape</name>
			<text>Evolution Mankey {R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Mankey you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Menace
Tantrum — At the beginning of each end step, if Primeape dealt damage this turn, put a +1/+1 counter on Primeape. Otherwise, remove a +1/+1 counter from Primeape.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/83.png" num="137">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Boar Ape</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Growlithe</name>
			<text>Intimidate (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by artifact creatures and/or creatures that share a color with it.)
Helping Hand — Growlithe gets +1/+2 as long as you control a Trainer.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/84.png" num="116">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dog</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hisuian Growlithe</name>
			<text>Intimidate,vigilance (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by artifact creatures and/or creatures that share a color with it.)
Take Down — Whenever Hisuian Growlithe and at least one other creature attack, up to one target creature can&apos;t block this turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/85.png" num="185">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dog</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>RW</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>WR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Arcanine</name>
			<text>Evolution Growlithe {R}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Growlithe you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Intimidate
Extreme Speed — Whenever a creature you control enters or becomes evolved, that creature gets +2/+0 and gains haste until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/86.png" num="104">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dog</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hisuian Arcanine</name>
			<text>Evolution Hisuian Growlithe {R}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Hisuian Growlithe you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Intimidate
Rock Slide — Whenever Hisuian Arcanine becomes evolved or attacks, you may have it deal 2 damage to each tapped creature target player controls.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/87.png" num="183">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dog</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RRW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>WR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Poliwag</name>
			<text>Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Damp — Whenever a blue pokémon enters or becomes evolved, scry 2. If this is the second time this ability has resolved this turn, it starts to rain.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/88.png" num="68">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Tadpole</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Poliwhirl</name>
			<text>Evolution Poliwag {U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Poliwag you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf
As long as it is raining, you may cast this card as thought it had flash.
Hypnosis — Whenever Poliwhirl enters or becomes evolved, tap up to one target creature and put a stun counter on it.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/89.png" num="69">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Tadpole</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Poliwrath</name>
			<text>Evolution Poliwhirl {U}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Poliwhirl you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf
Dynamic Punch — Whenever Poliwrath deals combat damage to a player, draw a card and goad up to one target creature that player controls.
As long as it is raining, other blue creatures you control get +1/+1.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/90.png" num="203">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Tadpole</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UUR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Abra</name>
			<text>Teleport — When Abra becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, you may pay {1}, if you do Abra phases out. (Treat it and anything attached to it as though they don&apos;t exist until its controller&apos;s next turn.)</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/91.png" num="34">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>0/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Kadabra</name>
			<text>Evolution Abra {1}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Abra you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Calm Mind — Whenever you cast a instant or sorcery spell, scry 1. If this is the second time this ability has resolved this turn, draw a card.
Whenever Kadabra becomes evolved, draw two cards.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/92.png" num="56">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alakazam</name>
			<text>Evolution Kadabra {1}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Kadabra you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Kinesis — Whenever an opponent casts a noncreature spell, counter it unless they pay {1}, if a spell is not countered this way, draw a card.
At the beginning of your end step, if Alakazam has one or more cards under it, return target instant or sorcery card from your graveyard to your hand.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/93.png" num="35">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UUU</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Alakazam</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Alakazam {3}{U}{U} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Alakazam you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
If you would draw a card except the first one you draw in each of your draw steps, draw two cards instead.
Psyshock — When Mega Alakazam becomes evolved, until the start of your next turn you may cast instant and sorcery spells from your hand without paying their mana costs.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/94.png" num="61">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5UUU</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Machop</name>
			<text>Power-Up Punch — Whenever Machop attacks, put a +1/+1 counter on Machop.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/95.png" num="122">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fighter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Machoke</name>
			<text>Evolution Machop {1}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Machop you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Vital Throw — You may exert Machoke as it attacks. When you do, Machoke fights target creature you don&apos;t control. (An exerted creature won&apos;t untap during your next untap step.)</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/96.png" num="121">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fighter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2RR</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Machamp</name>
			<text>Evolution Machoke {2}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Machoke you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever Machamp attacks, if it has one or more cards under it, it gains double strike until end of turn.
Steadfast  — At the beginning of your end step, if Machamp attacked this turn, you may untap Machamp.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/97.png" num="120">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fighter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Machamp</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Machamp {4}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Machamp you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Trample 
G-Max Chi Strike — When Gigantamax Machamp becomes evolved, creatures you control gain double strike and &quot;At the begining of your end step, untap this creature.&quot;until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/98.png" num="114">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Fighter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>10/10</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Bellsprout</name>
			<text>Reach
When Bellsprout enters, if you control another plant, it becomes sunny.
Growth — Whenever a land enters the battlefield under your control, put a Seed counter on up to one target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/99.png" num="168">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>BG</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Weepinbell</name>
			<text>Evolution Bellsprout {B}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Bellsprout you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Acid — Whenever Weepinbell becomes evolved or attacks, you may put a -1/-1 counter on up to one target creature. If that creature has a Seed counter on it, put three -1/-1 counters on that creature instead.
As long as it is sunny, you may cast this card as thought it had flash.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/100.png" num="213">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2BG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Victreebel</name>
			<text>Evolution Weepinbell {G}{G}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Weepinbell you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever Victreebel attacks, up to one target creature an opponent controls must block Victreebel if able.
Gastro Acid — Whenever Victreebel is blocked, put a -1/-1 counter on each creature blocking it. If Victreebel has one or more cards under it, when a creature blocking Victreebel dies, you gain 2 life and target opponent loses 2 life, if it is sunny, put a +1/+1 counter on Victreebel.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/101.png" num="211">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2BBGG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Victreebel</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Victreebel {3}{B}{G} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Victreebel you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Menace
Sludge Bomb — When Mega Victreebel becomes evolved, put two -1/-1 counters on all creatures your opponents control.
Whenever -1/-1 counter is put on a creature an opponent controls, that creatures controller loses 1 life and you gain 1 life.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/102.png" num="194">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4BBGG</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/8</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Tentacool</name>
			<text>Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
When Tentacool enters, if you control two or more other blue pokémon, it starts to rain.
Drifting — Whenever a blue creature enters the battlefield under your control or becomes evolved, you may pay {1}. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/103.png" num="206">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Jellyfish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>UB</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>UB</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Tentacruel</name>
			<text>Evolution Tentacool {1}{U}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Tentacool you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
At the beginning of your upkeep, if it is raining, surveil 2.
Acid — When Tentacruel becomes evolved, distribute up to X -1/-1 counters among any number of target creatures, where X is equal to the number of blue creatures in your graveyard and under your control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/104.png" num="207">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Jellyfish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4UB</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>UB</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Geodude</name>
			<text>Sturdy (This creature enters with a shield counter on it.)
Rock Collecting — Whenever Geodude enters or becomes evolved, if an opponent controls more lands than you, you may search your library for a basic land card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/105.png" num="178">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Golem</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>GW</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Geodude</name>
			<text>Sturdy (This creature enters with a shield counter on it.)
Galvanize — Whenever a land enters the battlefield under your control, put a charge counter on Alolan Geodude.
Whenever Alolan Geodude blocks or becomes blocked, you may remove X charge counters from Alolan Geodude, deal X damage to target creature blocking or blocked by Alolan Geodude.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/106.png" num="162">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Golem</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>RW</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>WR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Graveler</name>
			<text>Evolution Geodude {G}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Geodude you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Sturdy (This creature enters with a shield counter on it.)
When Graveler becomes evolved, a sandstorms rages.
Rollout — Whenever Graveler attacks, you may tap X number of untapped lands you control, Graveler gets +X/+0 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/107.png" num="182">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Golem</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2GW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Graveler</name>
			<text>Evolution Alolan Geodude {R}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Alolan Geodude you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Sturdy (This creature enters with a shield counter on it.)
Charge — Whenever Alolan Graveler attacks, put a charge counter on it.
Alolan Graveler has trample as long as it has four or more charge counters on it.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/108.png" num="164">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Golem</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2RW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Golem</name>
			<text>Evolution Graveler {1}{G}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Graveler you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Trample, sturdy (This creature enters with a shield counter on it.)
Whenever Golem becomes evolved, if a sandstorm rages, you may search your library for a basic land card, put that card onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle.
Avalanche — Whenever a land enters the battlefield under your control, creatures you control get +1/+1 until end of turn. Then if there is a Graveler card under this creature, put a shield counter on each creature you control. Then if there is a Geodude card under this creature, put a +1/+1 counter on each creature you control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/109.png" num="181">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Golem Turtle</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3GWW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Golem</name>
			<text>Evolution Alolan Graveler {R}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Alolan Graveler you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Vigilance, sturdy (This creature enters with a shield counter on it.)
Whenever Alolan Golem attacks, if it does not have a charge counter on it, put a charge counter on it. Otherwise, double the number of charge counters on Alolan Golem
Electromagnetic Catapult — {R}{W},{T}: Alolan Golem deals damage to the number of charge counters on it to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/110.png" num="163">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Golem Turtle</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RWW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>WR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ponyta</name>
			<text>Haste
Stomp — Whenever Ponyta attacks with two or more other creatures, Ponyta gains +1/+1 and trample until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/111.png" num="136">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Horse</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Ponyta</name>
			<text>When Galarian Ponyta enters or becomes evolved, Scry 2, then draw a card.
Pastel Veil — Pokémon you control have ward {1}. (Whenever this creature becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, counter it unless that player pays {1}.)</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/112.png" num="45">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Horse</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rapidash</name>
			<text>Evolution Ponyta {R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Ponyta you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Haste
Flame Charge — Whenever Rapidash attacks, you may discard a card, if you do draw a card. If there is a creature under Rapidash, you may deal damage equal to the mana value of the discarded card to target creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/113.png" num="139">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Horse</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Rapidash</name>
			<text>Evolution Galarian Ponyta {W}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Galarian Ponyta you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Vigilance, Ward {2}
As long as Galarian Rapidash has a card under it, it gains &quot;Whenever you draw a card, this creature gets +1/+0 until end of turn.&quot;
Psycho Cut — Whenever Galarian Rapidash attacks, draw a card then you gain life equal to the number of cards in your hand.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/114.png" num="175">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Horse Fairy</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WUU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Slowpoke</name>
			<text>Slowpoke enters the battlefield tapped.
Tail-Fishing — At the beginning of your upkeep, scry 1. You may reveal the top card of your library, if it is a blue creature card, draw a card. If the revealed creature is called Shellder, put it onto the battlefield and then draw a card instead.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/115.png" num="76">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Salamander</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Slowpoke</name>
			<text>Slowpoke enters the battlefield tapped.
Amnesia — At the beginning of your upkeep, each player mills a card. If a blue creature card is milled this way, draw a card. If the card you milled is called Shellder, put it onto the battlefield, then draw a card instead.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/116.png" num="46">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Salamander</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Slowbro</name>
			<text>Evolution Slowpoke {U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Slowpoke you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Slowbro enters the battlefield tapped.
Yawn — At the beginning of your upkeep, put a stun counter on one target creature each player controls.If there is a creature under Slowbro, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/117.png" num="75">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Salamander Crab</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Slowbro</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Slowbro {3}{U}{U} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Slowbro you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
All creatures your opponents control enter the battlefield tapped.
Future Sight— At the beginning of your end step, draw a card, scry 2, then fateseal 2.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/118.png" num="64">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Salamander Crab</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5UUU</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/10</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Slowbro</name>
			<text>Evolution Galarian Slowpoke {U}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Galarian Slowpoke you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Shell Side Arm — Whenever Galarian Slowbro becomes evolved or attacks, surveil 2. If there is a creature under Galarian Slowbro, put a -1/-1 counter on each tapped creature target player controls.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/119.png" num="176">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Salamander Crab</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>UB</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Magnemite</name>
			<text>Sturdy (This creature enters with a shield counter on it.)
Whenever another artifact or red creature enters the battlefield under your control, put a charge counter on Magnemite.
Thundershock — Remove three charge counters from Magnemite: Magnemite deals 2 damage to any target.
A deck can have any number of cards named Magnemite.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/120.png" num="124">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Pokémon Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Magneton</name>
			<text>Evolution Magnemite {1}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Magnemite you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Sturdy (This creature enters with a shield counter on it.)
Whenever Magneton becomes evolved, you may put up to two cards with Magnemite in their name from your field or graveyard under Magneton, then create X Treasure tokens where X is the number of cards under Magneton.
Magnet Pull — {2}{R}, Discard a card: Return target artifact from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/121.png" num="125">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Pokémon Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RRR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Farfetch&apos;d</name>
			<text>Leek — When Farfetch&apos;d enters, create colorless Equipment artifact token named Leek. It has &quot;Equipped creature gets +1/+0,&quot; &quot;As long as equipped creature is attacking, it has first strike&quot; and equip {1}, then attach it to Farfetch&apos;d.
Whenever Farfetch&apos;d attacks alone, draw a card. Farfetch&apos;d gains flying until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/122.png" num="10">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2W</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Farfetch&apos;d</name>
			<text>Leek — When Galarian Farfetch&apos;d enters, create colorless Equipment artifact token named Leek. It has &quot;Equipped creature gets +1/+0,&quot; &quot;As long as equipped creature is attacking, it has first strike&quot; and equip {1} , then attach it to Galarian Farfetch&apos;d.
Whenever Galarian Farfetch&apos;d attacks alone, put a +1/+1 counter on Galarian Farfetch&apos;d. Galarian Farfetch&apos;d gains trample until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/123.png" num="111">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Doduo</name>
			<text>Doduo has flying as long as you control, three or more birds.
Fury Attack — Whenever Doduo attacks, tap target creature defending player controls.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/124.png" num="8">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2W</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dodrio</name>
			<text>Evolution Doduo {1}{W}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Doduo you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Vigilance
Tri-Attack — Whenever Dodrio attacks, choose one at random. If Dodrio has a card under it, choose all three instead. —
• Put two stun counters on up to one target creature.
• Dodrio gains triple strike (This creature deals first-strike, regular, and last-strike combat damage.)
• Deal damage equal to Dodrio&apos;s power to up to one target creature if it is tapped.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/125.png" num="7">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WW</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Seel</name>
			<text>Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Seel has +1/+1 as long as it is raining.
Headbutt — Whenever Seel deals combat damage to a player, put a stun counter on up to one target creature that player controls. If that creature has two or more stun counters on it, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/126.png" num="73">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Seal</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1UU</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dewgong</name>
			<text>Evolution Seel {U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Seel you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf
Dewgong has +1/+1 as long as it is snowing.
Aurora Beam — Whenever Dewgong enters or becomes evolved, return up to one target creature to its owners hand.
Whenever a creature with a stun counter is returned to its owners hand, draw a card. This ability triggers only once each turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/127.png" num="41">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Creature — Pokémon Seal</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Grimer</name>
			<text>Wither (This deals damage to creatures in the form of -1/-1 counters.)
Sludge — Whenever Grimer, attacks or becomes evolved, put a -1/-1 counter on target creature an opponent controls. 
Whenever one or more -1/-1 counters would be put on Grimer, put a +1/+1 counter on Grimer instead.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/128.png" num="93">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Ooze</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Grimer</name>
			<text>Chemical Sludge — Whenever Alolan Grimer, attacks or becomes evolved, exile target card from a graveyard with a sludge counter on it and put a +1/+1 counter on Alolan Grimer.
{B}:Regenerate Alolan Grimer.
{2}, Put a card with a sludge counter from exile into its owners graveyard: Draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/129.png" num="82">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Ooze</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Muk</name>
			<text>Evolution Grimer {B}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Grimer you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Wither
Toxic Sludge — At the beginning of each opponent&apos;s upkeep, that player puts a -1/-1 counter on a creature they control. If that player can&apos;t, that player discard a card instead.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/130.png" num="97">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Ooze</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Muk</name>
			<text>Evolution Alolan Grimer {B}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Alolan Grimer you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Absorb 2 (If a source would deal damage to this creature, prevent 2 of that damage.)
Whenever Alolan Muk, attacks or becomes evolved, exile up to one target card from each players graveyard with a sludge counter on them.
Power of Alchemy — You may play lands and cast noncreature spells from among cards you exiled that have sludge counters on them, and you may spend mana as though it were mana of any color to cast those spells.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/131.png" num="84">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Ooze</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Shellder</name>
			<text>You may choose not to untap Shellder during your untap step.
Whenever Shellder enters, if you control a creature named Slowpoke or Galarian Slowpoke, you may search your library for a either a creature named Slowbro or Galarian Slowbro and put it into your hand.
Clamp — {U}, {T}: For as long as Shellder remains tapped, target tapped creature doesn&apos;t untap during its controller&apos;s untap step.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/132.png" num="74">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Oyster</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>0/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Cloyster</name>
			<text>Evolution Shellder {U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Shellder you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Shell Armor — At the beginning of your upkeep and whenever Cloyster becomes evolved, if Cloyster has a card under it, put a shield counter on Cloyster.
Whenever Cloyster attacks, you may return target tapped creature to its owners hand.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/133.png" num="40">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Creature — Pokémon Oyster</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gastly</name>
			<text>Shadow (This creature can block or be blocked by only creatures with shadow.)
Spite — Whenever Gastly deals combat damage to a player, that player discards a card.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/134.png" num="89">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Spirit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Haunter</name>
			<text>Evolution Gastly {B}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Gastly you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Shadow, Haunt (When this creature dies, exile it haunting target creature.)
Curse — Creatures haunted by Haunter have &quot;At the beginning of your upkeep, you lose life equal to the number of creatures haunting this creature.&quot;
When the creature Haunter haunts dies, return all creatures haunting it to their owners hand.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/135.png" num="94">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Spirit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2BB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gengar</name>
			<text>Evolution Haunter {1}{B}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Haunter you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Shadow (This creature can block or be blocked by only creatures with shadow.)
Night Shade — Whenever Gengar becomes evolved, up to one target creature gets -X/-X where X is equal to this creatures mana value.
Whenever a Spirit enters the battlefield under your control, target player loses 1 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/136.png" num="90">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Spirit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4BB</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Gengar</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Gengar {3}{B}{B} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Gengar you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Shadow (This creature can block or be blocked by only creatures with shadow.)
Phantom Gate — At the beginning of your end step, you may phase out any number of spirit creatures you control, target player loses life equal to the number of creatures phased out this way.
When Mega Gengar becomes evolved, return target spirit creature from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/137.png" num="96">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Spirit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5BBB</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Gengar</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Gengar {3}{B}{B}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Gengar you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Shadow 
G-Max Terror — When Gigantamax Gengar becomes evolved, phase out all creatures you don&apos;t control. Those creatures do not phase in as long as you control Gigantamax Gengar.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/138.png" num="91">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Spirit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7BBB</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>8/8</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Onix</name>
			<text>Sturdy, Dig (This creature enters with a shield counter on it. At the beginning of your end step, if this creature has attacked this turn, it phases out.)
Rock Tomb — When Onix enters or becomes evolved, up to one target creature can&apos;t attack or block until the start of your next turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/139.png" num="201">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Snake</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2GW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Drowzee</name>
			<text>Hypnosis — {1}{U}{U}: Tap target creature. Put a stun counter on it.
{U}, Remove a stun counter from target creature: Draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/140.png" num="42">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Beast</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hypno</name>
			<text>Evolution Drowzee {U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Drowzee you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever Hypno becomes evolved, put a stun counter on up to two target creatures.
Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, put a stun counter on up to one target creature.
Dream Eater — Whenever a stun counter is removed from a creature, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/141.png" num="54">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Beast</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Krabby</name>
			<text>Vice-Grip — Whenever Krabby attacks, if you control another blue pokémon, Krabby gets +2/+0 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/142.png" num="58">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Crab</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Kingler</name>
			<text>Evolution Krabby {1}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Krabby you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Crabhammer — Whenever Kingler attacks, you may exert it, return up to one target creature with mana value less than Kinglers power to its owners hand. If Kingler has one or more creatures under it, you may active this effect without exerting Kingler.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/143.png" num="57">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Crab</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4UU</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Kingler</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Kingler {3}{U}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Kingler you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Menace
G-Max Foam Burst — When Gigantamax Kingler becomes evolved, tap all creatures you don&apos;t control, they don&apos;t untap during their controllers next untap step.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/144.png" num="48">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Crab</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7UUU</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>10/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Voltorb</name>
			<text>Haste
Charge — Whenever Voltorb attacks, put a charge counter on it.
{T}, Remove two charge counters from Voltorb: Add {R}{R}.
When Voltorb dies, it deals damage equal to its power plus the number of charge counters on it to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/145.png" num="140">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hisuian Voltorb</name>
			<text>Rollout — Whenever Hisuian Voltorb attacks, put a +1/+1 counter on it.
When Hisuian Voltorb dies, it deals damage equal to its power to any target. If it deals 4 or more damage this way, you may search your library for a basic land card, put it onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/146.png" num="186">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Construct Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>RG</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>RG</colors>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Electrode</name>
			<text>Evolution Voltorb {R}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Voltorb you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Haste
Whenever Electrode becomes evolved or attacks, if it does not have a charge counter on it, put a charge counter on it. Otherwise, double the number of charge counters on it.
Explosion — Sacrifice Electrode: Electrode deals damage equal to its power plus the number of charge counters on it to each player and each creature they control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/147.png" num="109">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hisuian Electrode</name>
			<text>Evolution Hisuian Voltorb {R}{R}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Hisuian Voltorb you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever you cast a creature spell, put a +1/+1 counter on Hisuian Electrode.
Chloroblast — You may exert Hisuian Electrode as it attacks. When you do, remove all +1/+1 counters from Hisuian Electrode and deal X damage to any target where X is twice the number of counters removed this way.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/148.png" num="184">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Construct Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>RG</colors>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Exeggcute</name>
			<text>At the bringing of your upkeep, if you control three or more pokémon plants, draw a card, it becomes sunny.
Barrage — Whenever Exeggcute attacks, put a seed counter on target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/149.png" num="173">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant Egg</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1GU</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>UG</colors>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Exeggutor</name>
			<text>Evolution Exeggcute {1}{G}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Exeggcute you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever a seed counter is placed on a creature you don&apos;t control, draw a card. This ability triggers only twice each turn.
Hypnosis — Whenever you draw your second card each turn, put a stun counter on target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/150.png" num="174">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3GU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>UG</colors>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Exeggutor</name>
			<text>Evolution Exeggcute {1}{R}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Exeggcute you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Reach
Dragon Hammer — Whenever Alolan Exeggutor attacks, if it is sunny, Alolan Exeggutor gets +1/+1 and trample until end of turn.
Whenever a land enters the battlefield under your control, put a +1/+1 counter on another target plant you control.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/151.png" num="161">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant Dragon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4RG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>RG</colors>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Cubone</name>
			<text>When Cubone enters or becomes evolved, if a creature died this turn, put two +1/+1 counters on Cubone.
Bone Club — Whenever Cubone attacks, if it is equipped or attacks alone, Cubone gains trample and you may return up to one target land from your graveyard to your hand.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/152.png" num="147">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2G</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Marowak</name>
			<text>Evolution Cubone {2}{G} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Cubone you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
When Marowak enters or becomes evolved, return up to one target pokémon from your graveyard to your hand.
Bonemerang — Whenever another creature you control dies, you may have Marowak fight target creature you don&apos;t control. (Each deals damage equal to its power to the other.)</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/153.png" num="151">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3GG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Alolan Marowak</name>
			<text>Evolution Cubone {1}{B}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Cubone you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever another Pokémon you control dies, you may pay {B}{R}. If you do, create a token that&apos;s a copy of that creature, except it&apos;s a 1/1 red Spirit creature in addition to its other types.
Shadow Bone — {R}{B}: Exile target card from a graveyard. If it was a creature card, Alolan Marowak deals 2 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/154.png" num="165">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>BR</colors>
				<coloridentity>BR</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hitmonlee</name>
			<text>Haste
High-Jump Kick — You may exert Hitmonlee as it attacks. When you do, Hitmonlee gets +3/-3 and gains flying until end of turn. (An exerted creature won&apos;t untap during your next untap step.)
Whenever you exert another Pokémon, it gets +2/+0 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/155.png" num="118">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fighter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hitmonchan</name>
			<text>First strike
You may exert Hitmonchan as it attacks. Choose one —
• Thunder Punch — Pay {R}, if you do Hitmonchan gets +1/+0 until end of turn and deals 2 damage to any target.
• Comet Punch — Pay {1}, if you do Hitmonchan gains double strike until end of turn.
• Fire Punch — Pay {1}{R}, if you do Hitmonchan gets +2/+0 until end of turn and add {R}{R}{R}. Until end of turn, you don&apos;t lose this mana as steps and phases end.
Whenever you exert another Pokémon, it gets +0/+2 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/156.png" num="117">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fighter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Lickitung</name>
			<text>Vigilance
Whenever Lickitung enters or attacks, you may tap target creature with toughness equal to or less than Lickitung&apos;s mana value and put a stun counter on it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/157.png" num="17">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Frog Beast</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3W</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Koffing</name>
			<text>Smog — Whenever Koffing enters or becomes evolved, put a -1/-1 counter on each creature target player controls.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/158.png" num="95">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Balloon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2B</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Weezing</name>
			<text>Evolution Koffing {1}{B}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Koffing you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Menace
Neutralizing Gas — During your turn, creatures with -1/-1 counters you don&apos;t control lose all abilities.
Whenever Weezing dies, distribute X -1/-1 counters among any number of target creatures, where X is equal to Weezing&apos;s power.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/159.png" num="102">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Balloon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Weezing</name>
			<text>Evolution Koffing {1}{W}{B} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Koffing you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Strange Steam  — Whenever Galarian Weezing becomes evolved or attacks, you may remove a counter from target creature you control. If you do, draw a card and gain 2 life.
Whenever a -1/-1 counter is placed on a creature, you gain 1 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/160.png" num="177">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Balloon Fairy</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>WB</colors>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rhyhorn</name>
			<text>Trample
Horn Attack — Whenever Rhyhorn attacks, it gets +1/+1 until end of turn. If a land has entered under your control this turn, Rhyhorn gets +2/+2 until end of turn instead.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/161.png" num="205">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Rhino</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2GW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rhydon</name>
			<text>Evolution Rhyhorn {1}{G}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Rhyhorn you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Vigilance
Horn Drill — Whenever Rhydon enters or becomes evolved, you may have Rhydon deal damage equal to its power plus the number of lands you control to target creature you don&apos;t control.
Whenever a land you control enters, prevent the next 1 damage dealt to each creature you control until the end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/162.png" num="204">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Rhino</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4GW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Chansey</name>
			<text>Whenever another creature you control enters, you gain 1 life.
Soft-Boiled — At the beginning of your end step, if you gained life this turn, you may remove any number of counters from another target creature you control, then put a +1/+1 counter on it and untap it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/163.png" num="4">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Egg</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Tangela</name>
			<text>Reach
At the beginning of your end step, if it is sunny, untap Tangela.
Bind —  Whenever Tangela attacks, tap up to one target creature with flying and put a stun counter on it.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/164.png" num="160">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Plant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2G</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Kangaskhan</name>
			<text>Vigilance
When Kangaskhan enters, create a 2/2 white baby pokémon creature token.
Kangaskhan gets +1/+1 for each baby pokémon you control.
Baby pokémon you control have ward {2}. (Whenever this creature becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, counter it unless that player pays {2}.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/165.png" num="16">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Kangaroo</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WW</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Kangaskhan</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Kangaskhan {3}{W}{W} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Kangaskhan you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
When Mega Kangaskhan becomes evolved, you may put a baby from your hand onto the field. Then put a +1/+1 counter on each baby you control.
Parental Bond — As long as you control a baby pokémon, Mega Kangaskhan has double strike.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/166.png" num="20">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Kangaroo</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5WWW</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Horsea</name>
			<text>Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
When Horsea enters, it starts to rain.
Smokescreen — Whenever Horsea deals combat damage to a player, creatures that player control get -1/-0 until the start of your next turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/167.png" num="53">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Seadra</name>
			<text>Evolution Horsea {U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Horsea you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Whirlpool — Whenever you cast your first noncreature spell each turn, tap up to one target creature and put stun counter on it. Then if it is raining, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/168.png" num="71">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Goldeen</name>
			<text>Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Whenever Goldeen deals combat damage to a player, it starts to rain. if it is already raining, draw a card instead.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/169.png" num="50">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Seaking</name>
			<text>Evolution Goldeen {U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Goldeen you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Whenever Seaking becomes evolved, you may return target creature to its owners hand.
Waterfall — As long as it is raining, attacking fish you control have +1/+0.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/170.png" num="72">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Staryu</name>
			<text>Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Illuminate — Whenever Staryu enters or becomes evolved, scry 2.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/171.png" num="79">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Starfish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1UU</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Starmie</name>
			<text>Evolution Staryu {1}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Staryu you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Cosmic Power — Whenever you scry, you may reveal a nonland card with mana value 3 or less from among the cards being looked at, you may cast that card. If you do, put all other cards you&apos;re looking at on the bottom of your library in any order.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/172.png" num="78">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Starfish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4UU</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Starmie</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Starmie {3}{U}{U} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Starmie you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Whenever Mega Starmie becomes evolved, scry 5.
Mysterious Evolution — Whenever you scry, you may reveal a nonland card from among the cards being looked at, you may cast that card without paying it&apos;s mana cost. If you do, put all other cards you&apos;re looking at on the bottom of your library in any order. Activate this effect once per turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/173.png" num="65">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Starfish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5UUU</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mr. Mime</name>
			<text>Flash
When Mr.Mime enters or becomes evolved, create a 0/3 white Wall creature token with defender and vanishing 3.
Barrier — {W},{T}: Create a 0/3 white Wall creature token with defender and vanishing 3.
Light Screen — {U}, {T}:Create a 0/2 blue Wall creature token with defender and vanishing 3. It has &quot;{0}: Change the target of target spell or ability with only a single target that targets another creature you control to this creature.&quot;.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/174.png" num="195">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fairy Clown</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Mr. Mime</name>
			<text>Flash
Ice Body — As long as it is snowing, Galarian Mr. Mime has ward {1}.
Whenever Galarian Mr. Mime enters or becomes evolved, tap up to two target creatures. Put a stun counter on each of them.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/175.png" num="44">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Creature — Pokémon Clown</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Scyther</name>
			<text>Flying
{1}{G}{G}, Return an unblocked attacking insect you control to your hand: Put Scyther onto the battlefield from your hand tapped and attacking.
X-Scissor  — Whenever Scyther deals combat damage to a player, you may draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/176.png" num="159">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3GG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Jynx</name>
			<text>Ward {1}
Lovely Kiss —Whenever Jynx deals combat damage to a player, tap target creature that player controls. Put a stun counter on it, if that creature is not a snow creature, put two stun counters on it instead.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/177.png" num="55">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Creature — Pokémon Wierd</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Electabuzz</name>
			<text>Haste
As long as Electabuzz has three or more charge counters on it, it gets +2/+2.
Electabuzz enters or attacks, put a charge counter on Electabuzz.
Thunder Punch — Remove three charge counters from Electabuzz: Electabuzz deals 4 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/178.png" num="108">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Beast Cat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2RR</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Magmar</name>
			<text>Flame Body — Whenever Magmar enters or attacks, add {R}. Until end of turn, you don&apos;t lose this mana as steps and phases end.
Whenever you cast a red spell using mana produced by Magmar, Magmar deals 2 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/179.png" num="123">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Elemental</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2RR</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Pinsir</name>
			<text>As long as you control another Insect, Pinsir gets +2/+0 and has trample.
Fury Cutter — Whenever Pinsir deals combat damage to a creature or player, put a +1/+1 counter on Pinsir.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/180.png" num="156">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Pinsir</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Pinsir {3}{G}{G} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Pinsir you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying
Aerilate — When Mega Pinsir becomes evolved, insects you control get +2/+2, flying and trample until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/181.png" num="152">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5GGG</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Tauros</name>
			<text>Intimidate (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by artifact creatures and/or creatures that share a color with it.)
Raging Bull — Whenever Tauros and at least one other creature attack, another target attacking creature you control gets +1/+1 and Tauros gains first strike until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/182.png" num="31">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Ox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1WW</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Paldean Tauros(Combat Breed)</name>
			<text>Intimidate (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by artifact creatures and/or creatures that share a color with it.)
Raging Bull — Whenever Paldean Tauros and at least one other creature attack, Paldean Tauros gains +2/+0 until end of turn.
When Paldean Tauros attacks, you may exert it. If you do, it fights target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/183.png" num="134">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Ox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1RR</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Paldean Tauros(Blaze Breed)</name>
			<text>Intimidate (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by artifact creatures and/or creatures that share a color with it.)
Raging Bull — Whenever Paldean Tauros and at least one other creature attack, Paldean Tauros deals 1 damage to the defending player and each creature they control.
When Paldean Tauros attacks, you may exert it. If you do, Paldean Tauros deals 2 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/184.png" num="133">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Ox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1RR</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Paldean Tauros(Aqua Breed)</name>
			<text>Intimidate
Raging Bull — Whenever Paldean Tauros and at least one other creature attack, creatures defending player controls get -1/-0 until end of turn.
When Paldean Tauros attacks, you may exert it. If you do, return target creature with power X or less to its owners hand, where X is equal to this creatures power.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/185.png" num="202">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Ox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1UR</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Magikarp</name>
			<text>Splash — {T}, Return Magikarp to its owners hand: Look at the top two cards of your library, you may reveal a card called Gyarados from among them and add it to your hand, put the rest of the cards on the bottom of your library in any order.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/186.png" num="60">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fish</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>0/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gyarados</name>
			<text>Evolution Magikarp {3}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Magikarp you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Intimidate, Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Dragon Rage — Whenever Gyarados becomes evolved, return up to two target permanents to their owners hands.
Whenever Gyarados deals combat damage to a player, return target permanent with mana value 3 or less that player controls to its owners hand.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/187.png" num="52">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Serpent</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4UU</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Gyarados</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Gyarados {3}{U}{B} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Gyarados you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Hyper Beam — Whenever Mega Gyarados becomes evolved, destroy target creature with mana value less than or equal to the number of cards in its controller&apos;s graveyard. Its controller loses life equal to it&apos;s mana value.
Whenever Mega Gyarados deals combat damage to a player, that player discards a card.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/188.png" num="191">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Serpent</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4UUBB</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>UB</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
				<pt>8/8</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Lapras</name>
			<text>Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Whenever Lapras attacks, up to one other target creature you control gains surf until end of turn. If that creature is a snow creature, it gets +1/+1 until end of turn.
Hydration —Whenever you cast a spell, if it&apos;s raining, draw a card. This ability triggers only once each turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/189.png" num="59">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Creature — Pokémon Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Lapras</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Lapras {3}{U}{U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Lapras you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
When Gigantamax Lapras becomes evolved, creatures you control become snow creatures until the beginning of your next turn.
G-Max Resonance — Snow creatures you control have hexproof and surf.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/190.png" num="49">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Snow Creature — Pokémon Giant Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7UUU</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>8/8</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ditto</name>
			<text>Transform — You may have Ditto enter as a copy of any nonland permanent on the battlefield, except its name is Ditto, and it has &quot;{2}: Ditto becomes a copy of any nonland permanent on the battlefield, except its name is Ditto, and it has this ability.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/191.png" num="1">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Shapeshifter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<pt>0/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Eevee</name>
			<text>Whenever Eevee enters the battlefield or becomes evolved, reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal a creature card with an Evolution cost, put it into your hand and the rest on the bottom of your library in a random order.
Adaptability — Whenever a creature you control becomes evolved, put a +1/+1 counter on it.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/192.png" num="9">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Eevee</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Eevee {4}{W}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Eevee you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Lifelink
When Gigantamax Eevee becomes evolved, search your library for up to three creature cards with an Evolution Eevee cost, reveal them, then put them into your hand.
G-Max Cuddle — Creatures can&apos;t attack you unless their controller pays {2} for each creature they control that&apos;s attacking you.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/193.png" num="12">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7WWW</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Vaporeon</name>
			<text>Evolution Eevee {U}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Eevee you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
As long as it is raining, Vaporeon has ward {1}.
Evolutionary Swirl — Whenever a pokémon you control becomes evolved or Vaporeon attacks, scry 1, then draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/194.png" num="80">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3U</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Jolteon</name>
			<text>Evolution Eevee {R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Eevee you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Haste
Evolutionary Thunder — Whenever a pokémon you control becomes evolved or Jolteon attacks, put a charge counter on Jolteon. Then deal 1 damage to each opponent and each creature they control.
Remove three charge counters from Jolteon: Jolteon deals 4 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/195.png" num="119">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Flareon</name>
			<text>Evolution Eevee {R}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Eevee you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Evolutionary Flame — Whenever a pokémon you control becomes evolved or Flareon attacks, add {R}{R}. Until end of turn, you don&apos;t lose this mana as steps and phases end.
Whenever you spend mana produced by a pokémon to cast a creature spell, Flareon deals 2 damage to up to one target creature.
{R}: Flareon gets +1/+0 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/196.png" num="110">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fox</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Porygon</name>
			<text>Creatures that share a colour with Porygon get +1/+1.
Whenever Porygon becomes one or more colours, scry 1.
Conversion — {1}: Choose a colour. Porygon becomes that color until the start of your next turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/197.png" num="2">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Helix Fossil</name>
			<text>At the beginning of your upkeep or when it starts to rain, you may look at the top card of your library. If it&apos;s a fossil card, you may reveal it and put it into your hand.
{1}, Exile a card from your graveyard: Return target fossil from your graveyard to your hand. Activate this ability only if this card is a creature.
{T}: Add one mana of any colour. Activate this ability only if this card is not a creature.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/198.png" num="223">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Kindred Artifact — Fossil</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>3</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Omanyte</name>
			<text>Restore Helix Fossil {W}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Restore cost, put it over target artifact named Helix Fossil you own. It becomes an restored creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever Omanyte becomes restored or evolved, it starts to rain.
Shell Armor — Whenever another fossil you control enters, put a +1/+1 counter on up to one fossil creature you control.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/199.png" num="199">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fossil Squid</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Omastar</name>
			<text>Evolution Omanyte {2}{W}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Omanyte you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Prehistoric Swirl — Whenever Omastar becomes evolved, put the top card of each non-fossil creature on the bottom of their owners&apos; libraries.
Whenever rain begins or whenever Omastar attacks while it is raining, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/200.png" num="200">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fossil Squid</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4WU</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dome Fossil</name>
			<text>Whenever another fossil enters under your control or it starts to rain, if Dome Fossil is a creature and doesn&apos;t have a shield counter on it, put a shield counter on it. (If it would be dealt damage or destroyed, remove a shield counter from it instead.)
{1}, {T}: Reveal the top three cards of your library. Put all Fossil cards revealed this way into your hand and the rest into your graveyard.
{T}: Add one mana of any colour. Activate this ability only if this card is not a creature.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/201.png" num="220">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Kindred Artifact — Fossil</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>3</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Kabuto</name>
			<text>Restore Dome Fossil {W}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Restore cost, put it over target artifact named Dome Fossil you own. It becomes an restored creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever Kabuto becomes restored or evolved, it starts to rain.
Work Together— Whenever Kabuto attacks, if you control another Fossil, Kabuto gets +2/+0 and first strike until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/202.png" num="188">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fossil Crab</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Kabutops</name>
			<text>Evolution Kabuto {2}{W}{U} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Kabuto you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Surf (This creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with surf or flying.)
Kabutops has lifelink as long as it is raining.
Prehistoric Presence— Whenever Kabutops becomes evolved, non-fossil creatures can&apos;t attack until the start of your next turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/203.png" num="189">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fossil Crab</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4WU</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Old Amber</name>
			<text>Whenever Old Amber enters, gain X life where X is the number of fossils you control.
Whenever you attack with one or more fossil creatures, you may pay {2}, if you do scry X, where X is equal to the number of fossils you control, then draw a card. Activate this ability only if this card is a creature.
{T}: Add one mana of any colour. Activate this ability only if this card is not a creature.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/204.png" num="224">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Kindred Artifact — Fossil</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>3</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Aerodactyl</name>
			<text>Restore Old Amber {1}{W}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Restore cost, put it over target artifact named Old Amber you own. It becomes an restored creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying, Ward {1} (Whenever this creature becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, counter it unless that player pays {1}.)
Prehistoric Scream — Whenever Aerodactyl becomes restored or evolved, you may return target fossil from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/205.png" num="3">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Fossil Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WW</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Aerodactyl</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Aerodactyl {3}{W}{W} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Aerodactyl you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying, ward {2} (Whenever this creature becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, counter it unless that player pays {2}.)
Tough Claws — Whenever Mega Aerodactyl or another Fossil creature you control deals combat damage to a player, put a +1/+1 counter on that creature.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/206.png" num="18">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Fossil Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5WWW</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Snorlax</name>
			<text>Vigilance
Snorlax enters the battlefield tapped with three stun counters on it.
As long as Snorlax has a stun counter on it, prevent all damage that would be dealt to it.
Whenever you sacrifice a Food, put a stun counter and a +1/+1 counter on Snorlax.
Obstacle — As long as Snorlax has a stun counter on it, it can block as though it were untapped.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/207.png" num="29">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Bear</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WWW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gigantamax Snorlax</name>
			<text>Gigantamax Snorlax {3}{W}{W}{W} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Gigantamax cost, put it over target Snorlax you own and put 3 G-MAX counters on it. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it. At the beginning of your end step, remove a G-MAX counter from it. When the last is removed, return the top card of it to the bottom of your library.)
Trample
If an ability would trigger from sacrificing food, that ability triggers an additional time.
G-Max Replenish — Whenever Gigantamax Snorlax becomes evolved, remove all stun counters from it and untap it. Create a food berry token for each counter removed this way, then return all food from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/208.png" num="14">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Gigantamax Creature — Pokémon Giant Bear</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7WWW</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>12/12</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sitrus Berry</name>
			<text>When Sitrus Berry enters and when you sacrifice it, put a +1/+1 counter on target pokémon you control.
{2}, {T}, Sacrifice Sitrus Berry: You gain 3 life. This effect costs {2} less to activate if you control a pokémon that has been dealt damage this turn.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/209.png" num="225">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact — Food Berry</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>2</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Berry PKM</name>
			<text>{1}, {T}, Sacrifice Berry: You gain 2 life.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/210.png" num="1">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Token Artifact — Food Berry</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>2</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<token>1</token>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Haban Berry</name>
			<text>When you sacrifice Haban Berry, prevent all damage dealt by target dragon until the start of your next turn.
{2}, {T}, Sacrifice Haban Berry: You gain 3 life.</text>
			<set rarity="common" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/211.png" num="222">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact — Food Berry</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>2</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Articuno</name>
			<text>Flying, ward {2}
Blizzard — Whenever Articuno enters or attacks, it starts to snow. Then tap up to two target creatures and put a stun counter on each of them.
Stun counters can&apos;t be removed from permanents your opponents control.
Snow creatures you control have &quot;Whenever this creature deals combat damage to a player, draw a card.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/212.png" num="39">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Snow Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4UU</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Articuno</name>
			<text>Flash
Flying
Whenever Galarian Articuno enters, counter target creature spell. Draw cards equal to that spell&apos;s mana value.
Freezing Glare — Whenever Galarian Articuno attacks,you may tap target creature. If you do, put a stun counter on it.
{U}{U}: Return Galarian Articuno to its owners hand.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/213.png" num="43">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4UU</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Zapdos</name>
			<text>Flying, ward {2}
Once during each of your turns, you may cast an instant or sorcery spell from your graveyard with mana value less than or equal to the number of charge counters on Zapdos.
Thunderstorm — Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, put a charge counter on Zapdos if this is the first time this ability has resolved this turn. If it&apos;s the second time, Zapdos deals 2 damage to each creature target player controls. If it&apos;s the third time, creatures you control gain +2/+0 and haste until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/214.png" num="142">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4RR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Zapdos</name>
			<text>Trample, haste
Thunderous Kick — Whenever Galarian Zapdos attacks, it gets +1/+0 for each other attacking creature you control and can&apos;t be blocked by creatures without flying until end of turn.
Whenever Galarian Zapdos deals combat damage to a player, untap all creatures you control. After this phase, there is an additional combat phase. This ability triggers only once each turn.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/215.png" num="112">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4RR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Moltres</name>
			<text>Flying, ward {2}
Whenever Moltres enters or attacks, exile the top two cards of your library. You may cast the exiled cards until the end of your next turn.
Wildfire — Whenever Moltres deals combat damage to a player, add {R}{R}{R}. Until end of turn, you don&apos;t lose this mana as steps and phases end.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/216.png" num="131">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4RR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Galarian Moltres</name>
			<text>Flying
Whenever a creature an opponent controls dies during your turn, that creatures controller discards a card. This ability triggers only once each turn for each player.
Fiery Wrath — When Galarian Moltres enters, creatures with mana value 5 or less get -4/-4 until the end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/217.png" num="88">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Pokémon Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4BB</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dratini</name>
			<text>Shed Skin — At the beginning of your end step, create a treasure token.</text>
			<set rarity="uncommon" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/218.png" num="172">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dragon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>UR</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dragonair</name>
			<text>Evolution Dratini {1}{U}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Dratini you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, draw a card, then if it was not a red or blue spell, discard a card.
Twister — Whenever Dragonair becomes evolved, return up to one target creature to its owners hand. Dragonair deals 2 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/219.png" num="170">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dragon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dragonite</name>
			<text>Evolution Dragonair {2}{U}{R} (If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Evolution cost, put it over target creature named Dragonair you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying
Special Delivery — Whenever Dragonite deals combat damage to a player, you may cast a spell with mana value 3 or less from your hand without paying it&apos;s mana cost.
{U}{U}: You may return another creature you control to its owner&apos;s hand. If you do, Dragonite gains hexproof until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/220.png" num="171">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Pokémon Dragon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3URR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Dragonite</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Dragonite {3}{U}{R} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Dragonite you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Flying, trample
Whenever Mega Dragonite becomes evolved, draw a card and then discard a card. If the discarded cards mana value is less than the number of cards in your hand, you may create a copy of that card and cast it without paying it&apos;s mana cost.
Sky Transport — Whenever Mega Dragonite attacks, creatures you control get +1/+1 and flying until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/221.png" num="190">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mega Creature — Pokémon Dragon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5URR</manacost>
				<cmc>8</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<pt>8/8</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mewtwo</name>
			<text>This spell can&apos;t be countered.
Ward {3}
Psychic Mastery — Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, choose one that has not been chosen this turn —
• Recover— Draw a card.
• Barrier —Mewtwo gains hexproof until end of turn.
• Telekinesis —Tap target creature. Put a stun counter on it.
• Psystrike —Return target nonland permanent to its owner&apos;s hand.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/222.png" num="67">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Pokémon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5UU</manacost>
				<cmc>7</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Mewtwo X</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Mewtwo {4}{U}{R} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Mewtwo you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Trample, Prowess
Aura Sphere — Whenever Mega Mewtwo X becomes evolved or attacks, reveal the top card of your library. If it&apos;s an instant or sorcery spell, you may cast it without paying its mana cost. Otherwise, put it into your hand.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/223.png" num="192">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Mega Creature — Pokémon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5UURR</manacost>
				<cmc>9</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<pt>9/9</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mega Mewtwo Y</name>
			<text>Mega Evolution Mewtwo {4}{U}{U} (You may cast this card for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost if you do not control a Mega Creature. If you cast this spell for it&apos;s Mega Evolution cost, put it over target Mewtwo you own. It becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.)
Psychic Infinity — Whenever you cast a pokémon spell, copy that spell. This ability triggers only once per turn. (A copy of a permanent spell becomes a token.)
Pokémon spells you cast from your hand have cascade.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/224.png" num="63">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Mega Creature — Pokémon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5UUUU</manacost>
				<cmc>9</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>8/8</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mew</name>
			<text>Flying
Mythical Genetics — As Mew enters or at the beginning of your upkeep, you may place a pokémon creature card from your hand or graveyard under Mew, Mew becomes an evolved creature and gains all abilities under it.
 {W}{U}{B}{R}{G}: Mill three cards. Return up to one pokémon creature from your graveyard to the battlefield. Then put a +1/+1 counter on each pokémon you control.</text>
			<set rarity="mythic" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/225.png" num="66">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Pokémon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UUU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>WUBRG</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>MissingNo.</name>
			<text>Flying
Item Duplication — Whenever you cast a spell, copy it. Then flip a coin. If you win the flip, repeat this process.
MissingNo.&apos;s power and toughness are each equal to the number of differently named permanents on the battlefield. 
Old man glitch — Miracle {WUB}{RG} (You may cast this card for its miracle cost when you draw it if it&apos;s the first card you drew this turn.)</text>
			<set rarity="special" picurl="https://M1ghtyGuard.github.io/sets/PKM-files/img/226.png" num="226">PKM</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Pokémon Glitch Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WUBRG</coloridentity>
				<pt>*/*</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
	</cards>
</cockatrice_carddatabase>